<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Tolis</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Tolis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:06:20 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Python Temperature Conversions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/python-temperature-conversions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:06:20 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/python-temperature-conversions/</guid>
      <description>This is a small app made in python using the tkinter library made in an hour or so, just to practice for my midterm exams. All this is really is a temeperature converions app from&#xA;Celsius to Fahrenheit Celsius to Kelvin Fahrenheit to Celsius Fahrenheit to Kelvin Kelvin to Celsius Kelvin to Fahrenheit There will be no update on this project, it was just a testing ground.&#xA;PS: I was not planning on putting this project on the spotlight here, but today I was browsing through old github projects and I said why not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jit Crowd Emulator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/jit-crowd-emulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 15:38:28 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/jit-crowd-emulator/</guid>
      <description>What is this? Jit Crowd Emulator is a python script that utilizes the Selenium browser automation suite to create an artificial crowd in your Jit.si meeting.&#xA;What are the capabilities of the artificial crowd? This crowd can:&#xA;Join meetings (even password protected ones). React using the Jit.si default reactions. Admit or reject other members from the lobby. The third item in the list gives this script a moderator bot attribute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temperature Conversions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/temperature-conversions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:56:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/temperature-conversions/</guid>
      <description>This program was made for my third semester java class. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple temperature conversions app. It can handle:&#xA;Celsius to Fahrenheit Celsius to Kelvin Fahrenheit to Celsius Fahrenheit to Kelvin Kelvin to Celsius Kelvin to Fahrenheit The assignmen&amp;rsquo;s feautres are done but the program is still work in progress, because I want to expand it, so you can expect certain features added.&#xA;We are currently on version 1.0.1 and some features to be expected are:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/siv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:56:03 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/siv/</guid>
      <description>SIV or else Simple Image Viewer is a small program writen in Java that enables the user to view images. This app is really simple and it is mostly directed to Linux users that access their files through the CLI and want an image viewer that can accept command line arguments. Of course this does not mean that the app does not have a GUI that enables the user to pick and view an image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/das/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:40:44 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Personal-Webpage/projects/das/</guid>
      <description>Development Assistant Script or else DAS is a simple script that will help YOU the developer download a variety of tools for the language that you develop on, much easier and faster. These tools will be a compiler or interpeter (depends on the language) and an editor or a full blown IDE in some cases.&#xA;This script was showcased by me, at an event that took place on 18/01/2023 on the AUTH campus, called &amp;ldquo;Εισαγωγή στα Linux και στο ανοικτό λογισμικό&amp;rdquo;, organized by me and members of the ACM AUTH Student Chapter and supported by two professor of the department of informatics of AUTH.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
